[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 17, "question": "Who do you think killed Bonny?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "think", "killed", "Bonny", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 18, "answer": "Bonny had people that she burned.", "answer_tokens": ["Bonny", "had", "people", "that", "she", "burned", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "Congress"]}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "What can you tell me about what happened to her?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "tell", "me", "about", "what", "happened", "to", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Well, Piers, as you know, something very similar happened to me when I was in Congress many years ago.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "as", "you", "know", ",", "something", "very", "similar", "happened", "to", "me", "when", "I", "was", "in", "Congress", "many", "years", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kerry"]}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "Have you managed to speak to her at all?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "managed", "to", "speak", "to", "her", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "I was with Kerry last week.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "with", "Kerry", "last", "week", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Would you categorize what she went through as the kind of thing that you were talking about in terms of people who get stigmatized and sensationalized?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "categorize", "what", "she", "went", "through", "as", "the", "kind", "of", "thing", "that", "you", "were", "talking", "about", "in", "terms", "of", "people", "who", "get", "stigmatized", "and", "sensationalized", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Well, listen, Piers, if she had been suffering from cancer, or diabetes or some other acceptable illness, she wouldn't have had any problem getting the necessary help.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "listen", ",", "Piers", ",", "if", "she", "had", "been", "suffering", "from", "cancer", ",", "or", "diabetes", "or", "some", "other", "acceptable", "illness", ",", "she", "would", "n't", "have", "had", "any", "problem", "getting", "the", "necessary", "help", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "How much of a pressure does the family feel about that kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "a", "pressure", "does", "the", "family", "feel", "about", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Well, Piers, like I said in my own circumstance, I was very fortunate.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "like", "I", "said", "in", "my", "own", "circumstance", ",", "I", "was", "very", "fortunate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "What can you tell me about them?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "tell", "me", "about", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Well, on the face of it, you're right, they seem damaging.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "on", "the", "face", "of", "it", ",", "you", "'re", "right", ",", "they", "seem", "damaging", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "Do you know if she is actually a relative or not?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "if", "she", "is", "actually", "a", "relative", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "According to the court's order, allowing for the release of her statement, I'm allowed to state the relationship.", "answer_tokens": ["According", "to", "the", "court", "'s", "order", ",", "allowing", "for", "the", "release", "of", "her", "statement", ",", "I", "'m", "allowed", "to", "state", "the", "relationship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Do you have any suspicions yourself as to why she came forward and said this now?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "suspicions", "yourself", "as", "to", "why", "she", "came", "forward", "and", "said", "this", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "There actually were some other events that happened in the family dynamics that we will get into if we need to.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "actually", "were", "some", "other", "events", "that", "happened", "in", "the", "family", "dynamics", "that", "we", "will", "get", "into", "if", "we", "need", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "CC", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "A family member alleging racism from George's family?", "question_tokens": ["A", "family", "member", "alleging", "racism", "from", "George", "'s", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "I think that if they could tie that to an event of George's and if, in fact, they had some other evidence supporting a suggestion of racism.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "if", "they", "could", "tie", "that", "to", "an", "event", "of", "George", "'s", "and", "if", ",", "in", "fact", ",", "they", "had", "some", "other", "evidence", "supporting", "a", "suggestion", "of", "racism", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "I presume after this huge dump of stuff today that feeling has been reinforced, is it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "presume", "after", "this", "huge", "dump", "of", "stuff", "today", "that", "feeling", "has", "been", "reinforced", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBG", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Well, actually, I had asked the state.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "actually", ",", "I", "had", "asked", "the", "state", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "Is it valid?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "valid", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "I would disagree with you, Piers, on that comment to smear.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "disagree", "with", "you", ",", "Piers", ",", "on", "that", "comment", "to", "smear", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "But why do you think it's this issue that President Obama feels so strongly is the key one?", "question_tokens": ["But", "why", "do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "this", "issue", "that", "President", "Obama", "feels", "so", "strongly", "is", "the", "key", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Well, look it, Governor Romney from the very beginning has said I have the credibility to be president because I ran a business.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", "it", ",", "Governor", "Romney", "from", "the", "very", "beginning", "has", "said", "I", "have", "the", "credibility", "to", "be", "president", "because", "I", "ran", "a", "business", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "I can accept the president who's a successful businessman?", "question_tokens": ["I", "can", "accept", "the", "president", "who", "'s", "a", "successful", "businessman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "They may.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "may", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "They judge him on his performance, don't they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "judge", "him", "on", "his", "performance", ",", "do", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "And what that means for the next four years because that's really what they're voting for.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "what", "that", "means", "for", "the", "next", "four", "years", "because", "that", "'s", "really", "what", "they", "'re", "voting", "for", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "What do you make though of the wider point that's being made there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "though", "of", "the", "wider", "point", "that", "'s", "being", "made", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Well, there's certainly a point to be made in politics about a man running for president who takes advantage of all these presumably perfectly legal things to reduce his income tax.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "certainly", "a", "point", "to", "be", "made", "in", "politics", "about", "a", "man", "running", "for", "president", "who", "takes", "advantage", "of", "all", "these", "presumably", "perfectly", "legal", "things", "to", "reduce", "his", "income", "tax", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "What could it be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "could", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Well, it's bizarre to me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "bizarre", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Is there a better one out there for him?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "better", "one", "out", "there", "for", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJR", "CD", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "I think probably the choice for vice president for Mitt Romney or any candidate is do no harm.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "probably", "the", "choice", "for", "vice", "president", "for", "Mitt", "Romney", "or", "any", "candidate", "is", "do", "no", "harm", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Would he be a sensible pick?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "he", "be", "a", "sensible", "pick", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "He'd be a sensible pick because, again, no one would notice or care.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'d", "be", "a", "sensible", "pick", "because", ",", "again", ",", "no", "one", "would", "notice", "or", "care", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "When you saw the interview, what went through your mind?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "saw", "the", "interview", ",", "what", "went", "through", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "A lot.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bonnie"]}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "You have absolutely no doubt that he killed Bonnie?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "absolutely", "no", "doubt", "that", "he", "killed", "Bonnie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "He did kill Bonnie.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "did", "kill", "Bonnie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bonnie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Why are you so certain because he got off the criminal case?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "so", "certain", "because", "he", "got", "off", "the", "criminal", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "How can you be sure that theory isn't the true one?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "you", "be", "sure", "that", "theory", "is", "n't", "the", "true", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "It's not accurate.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "accurate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "What's happened to his daughter?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "happened", "to", "his", "daughter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Well, in a nutshell, that was the motive.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "a", "nutshell", ",", "that", "was", "the", "motive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Do you think he should be allowed to?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "should", "be", "allowed", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "I have no opinion on that whatsoever.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "opinion", "on", "that", "whatsoever", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Potatoes"]}, "docId": "120716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "It's not about me, is it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "about", "me", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Yes, it is, because you opened the door, Charlie Potatoes, and you can take that to the bank.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "is", ",", "because", "you", "opened", "the", "door", ",", "Charlie", "Potatoes", ",", "and", "you", "can", "take", "that", "to", "the", "bank", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]